

COMPUTER SKILLS

FRONT-END:

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- React, Vue
- Adobe Photoshop

BACK-END:

- Java
- C#
- Python
- GoLang

DATABASE:

- MS SQL Server
- PL SQL

MISCELLANEOUS:

- NPM | Yarn
- Source Control (Git), Git Bucket
- Unit Test (IntellJ)
- JIRA, Trello
- 3DS Max

LANGUAGE

- •••• Kazakh
- •••• Russian
- •••• English
- •••• Turkish
- • German

COURSES

- Complete React JS Web Developer
- Full JavaScript
- DLD Conference for future leaders
- Machine Learning at Coursera

CONTACT ME AT



- urziya.dukenbay@gmail.com
- S urziya.dukenbay
- in @urziya-dukenbay
- udukenbay/

URZIYA DUKENBAY

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

I am a software developer who creates high-performing applications with organized architecture. Experienced in product design and client relations. Have goals to be a passionate inspiring and creative developer and leader that will be able to invent and innovate. Share and teach others in a way that they can be excited like I am.

PROGRESS

- Optimized department performance week work into system 20 minutes
- Building new process, new direction for the organization, with aims reaching 60% of the country market
- Volunteering for a startup, located in Malaysia

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

Kaspi Bank | Jul 2021 - present

- develop and lead algorithmic solutions to implement the task
- writing unit tests and debugging
- correct and improve the development of an already written process
- develop instructions, write technical documentation in the portal
- to be part of the development and implementation of new technologiess

Lead Engineer

GATE Insaat Taahhut Sanayi ve Ticaret | Nov 2017 - Jul 2021

- Product code using .NET languages (C#), upgrade, configure and debug the system, provide technical support
- Designed and build architecture of the database in MS SQL Server, monitor documentation, and provide daily, weekly reports
- Analyzing system and preparing monthly/weekly reports for management

Database and BI Developer

LLP Teksan | Feb 2017 - Oct 2017

- Created and supported database in MS SQL Server
- Maintained Tiger (SAP)
- Prepare KPI and BI reports (Datazen Dashboards). Analyzing sales and prioritizing sales according to sales reports at every city shop

Oracle Siebel CRM system developer

Borlas Kazakhstan | Aug 2016 - Dec 2016

• Supported and developed the system to customer requirements.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Suleyman Demirel University

Computer Science, B.Sc. | Sep 2012 - Jun 2016

- B.E., engineering and technology
- GPA: 3.53 (4.0). Diploma with honors
- Participated in enterprise project in KazMunayGas, as system administrator, Jun - Aug 2015